

contact@johnevanofski.net 720 938 4999

Oakland, Bay Area CA

http://johnevanofski.net

BIO

John Evanofski is a Bay Area web developer and designer with a diverse technological skillset and a problem solving aptitude. He is also an adept communicator and an experienced technology educator. His goal is to use his skills to bridge the gap between the user and the designer in order to continue the tradition of good design.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer
David Kerr Design / Oakland CA / 2012-2014

Web and Graphic Design Lead Clean LED Energy / Oakland CA / 2014

Web Developer and Tech Support YogaKula / Berkeley CA / 2012-2014

Freelance Web and Graphic Design Cindy Cleary Art / 2014 Mission Creek Festival / Oakland CA / 2013 SJ Sallinger Designs / San Francisco CA / 2013

Teaching

HTML & CSS, Computing / Tutor / Wyzant.com / 2014 WordPress / AcademyX / 2013 Excel '98 & 2010 / ServiceSource Inc / 2009-2013

SKILLS

WEB

- HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Ruby
- Responsive Web
- WordPress CMS

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- Dreamweaver

OTHER

- Final Cut Pro
- Microsoft Office Suite

EDUCATION

Liberal Arts Humanities (AA)
Digital Art Certificate
City College San Francisco / 2013

Web Design Certificate
AcademyX / 2011

